okay one of my ideas is again I don't
name things so I kind of name them based
on what they already are but is like
Facebook for neighborhoods just go
social media for neighborhoods something
right either but I had a bad experience
with one of my neighbors still kind of
ongoing whenever I parked behind him he
does crap to my car I think it's him I
think I know who it is and so far
because I kind of have a crappy car I've
just kind of let it go and kind of
better it's done to my card and everyone
else on the block but at the same time
like part of me wants to take vengeance
like eat his car and at the time I had a
child in diapers I'm like Willa you peed
on my car do you really like I have
access to much worse things much more
readily than you do but I did not just
do that
but part of what came out of that was I
was like God like if he could
communicate with me better and I could
communicate with him better I think we
would get a lot more like I think that
he'd be like one he wouldn't do those
things to my car because he'd realized
I'm like a single mom with a disability
who needs my car to be parked there or
at least can have my car parked there
like I live across the street and maybe
I'd understand his side better maybe he
has a really good reason for not wanting
me to part behind his car door nobody
parks and but more than that like to be
able to say hey I'm going on vacation
and not to all the Facebook Worthen
robbers like great I'll be by next
Wednesday but just my neighborhood say
hey I too know what your neighbors are
going through that someone's going
through cancer and you can bring them
over soup or a smoothie that someone
needs child care that someone just like
recreating those on neighborhoods that
we had generations ago or a generation
ago that we just don't have anymore I
don't have it ends Vancouver's not so
there are some neighborhoods I think
that are more intertwined and mine
definitely it's not that I would love it
to be in a way that's easily because
there can be one person who kind of
creates that for the neighborhood but
I'm not that personality and I would
like it to be easier with my current
personality because I don't want to
change my personality I would like to be
able to say hey let's have a potluck and
throw
out there and see like and not have to
go knock on everyone's door be like a
want to come out of a pod look and to be
able to say hey we have this community
space that what could we create with it
is there somewhere we can put a tool
shed that we can all share tools if you
all don't need an lawnmower kimete can
we combine lawn won't like can I go
everyone's lawn at once a year and
everyone does that every two weeks and
we only have to mow your lawn once here
you can get a ride on lot more to do
that with whatever happens to work as a
collective community what do we have
that we can share with each other and
done in a way that it's more secure
because it is people in your
neighborhood whether that's your work
neighborhood or your physical
neighborhood it's where you actually
live and so you get one right you don't
I mean I guess if you live in multiple
locations you can have multiple ones but
I think what the more we're able to
connect and share resources easily the
more we will thank you